let questions = [ 
    {
      numb: "Bohemian Rhapsody, Queen",
      question: "Just killed a man, put a gun against his head ________ now he's dead",
      answer: "pull my trigger",
        options: [
          "might be a killer 'cause",
          "pull my trigger", 
          "I cry in regret",
          "somethimg I wish I could undone",
        ],
      },
      {
        numb: "Dancing Queen, ABBA",
        question: "Dancing Queen, feel the beat ________",
        answer: "from the tambourine",
            options: [
            "from the music machine",
            "like the front-page of a magazine", 
            "venture into the unseen",
            "from the tambourine",
            ],
    },
      {
        numb: "Zapatillas, El Canto del Loco",
        question: "Me da pena tanta tontería, quiero un poquito de ________",
        answer: "normalidad",
            options: [
            "mundanidad",
            "humanidad", 
            "regularidad",
            "normalidad",
            ],
    },
    //   {
    //     numb: "Toxic, Bitney Spears",
    //     question: "It's getting late __________ I took a sip from my devil's cup",
    //     answer: "to give you up",
    //       options: [
    //         "to try to run",
    //         "to change your mind", 
    //         "to give you up",
    //         "to turn back",
    //       ],
    // },
    {
        numb: "Bailando, Alaska y Los Pegamoides",
        question: "Tengo los huesos desencajados, __________ tengo el cuerpo muy mal",
        answer: "el fémur tengo muy dislocado",
            options: [
            "los músculos tengo magullados",
            "el fémur tengo muy dislocado", 
            "todo el finde lo tengo ocupado",
            "río entre copas, balbuceando",
            ],
    },
    {
        numb: "Never Gonna Give You Up, Rick Astley",
        question: "Never gonna give you up, never gonna let you down, never gonna run around ________",
        answer: "and desert you",
            options: [
            "and desert you",
            "and leave you", 
            "and hurt you",
            "and betray you",
            ],
    },
    {
        numb: "La Chica de Ayer, Nacha Pop",
        question: "Te acuestas a mi lado sin saber por qué ________ te han visto crecer",
        answer: "las calles mojadas",
            options: [
            "las luces de las farolas",
            "son estas calles las que", 
            "los vecinos del barrio",
            "las calles mojadas",
            ],
    },
    {
        numb: "Embrujada, Tino Casal",
        question: "Sube al coche, reina de la noche y olvida ________",
        answer: "tu mal humor",
            options: [
            "tu mal humor",
            "todo tu dolor", 
            "aquél gran error",
            "tu corazón",
            ],
    },
    {
        numb: "Highway to Hell, AC/DC",
        question: "Hey satan ________ playin' in a rockin' band",
        answer: "payin' my dues",
            options: [
            "I'm on the promised land",
            "I'm doin' fine", 
            "livin' easy",
            "payin' my dues",
            ],
    },
    // {
    //     numb: "Message in a Bottle, The police",
    //     question: "Love can mend your life, or love can ______",
    //     answer: "break your heart",
    //         options: [
    //         "make you wanna die",
    //         "stop your heart", 
    //         "break your heart",
    //         "drown in hurt",
    //         ],
    // },
    
    // {
    //     numb: "Telephone, Lady GaGa ft. Beyoncé",
    //     question: "What did you say? Oh, ________? sorry, I cannot hear you I'm kinda busy",
    //     answer: "you're breaking up on me",
    //         options: [
    //         "you're breaking up on me",
    //         "you're telling me you love me", 
    //         "you say it's over and that you hate me",
    //         "you brought somebody home",
    //         ],
    // },
    // {
    //     numb: "Mi Gran Noche, Raphael",
    //     question: "Hoy, para mí, es un día especial, ________",
    //     answer: "hoy saldré por la noche",
    //         options: [
    //         "bailaré a la luz de los faroles",
    //         "veré lo que el sol desconoce", 
    //         "derpertaré cuando el sol ya se esconde",
    //         "hoy saldré por la noche",
    //         ],
    // },
    {
        numb: "Me Colé en una Fiesta, Mecano",
        question: "La vi pasar y me escondí, ________ iba provocando a la gente",
        answer: "con su traje transparente",
            options: [
            "con su traje transparente",
            "con sus ojos atrayentes", 
            "con su traje sugerente",
            "con su cuerpo ardiente",
            ],
    },
    {
        numb: "Zombie, The Cranberries",
        question: "When the violence causes _____ we must be mistaken",
        answer: "silence",
            options: [
            "quietness",
            "silence",
            "heartache", 
            "quietus",
            ],
    },
    {
        numb: "Sobreviviré, Mónica Naranjo",
        question: "___________, maquillaje hasta en el corazón",
        answer: "Pelo acrílico, cuero y tacón",
            options: [
            "Hoy me vestí de bufón",
            "Ojos oscuros y pintalabios chillón", 
            "Pelo acrílico, cuero y tacón",
            "Sonrisa fingida nubladas mi juicio y visión",
            ],
    },
    {
        numb: "Wannabe, Spice Girls",
        question: "If you wanna be my lover __________, make it last forever, friendship never ends",
        answer: "you gotta get with my friends",
            options: [
            "better make amends",
            "you better be prepares", 
            "you gotta get with my friends",
            "you'll have to meet my friends",
            ],
    },
    {
        numb: "Enamorado de la Moda Juvenil, Radio Futura",
        question: "Sí, yo caí enamorado de la moda juvenil de ________, de las chicas, de los maniquís",
        answer: "los chicos",
            options: [
            "las camisas",
            "los zapatos", 
            "la gente",
            "los chicos",
            ],
    },
    {
        numb: "Total Eclipse of the Heart, Bonnie Tyler",
        question: "Every now and then I get a little bit terrifried ________",
        answer: "and then I see the look in your eyes",
            options: [
            "body aching, tongue-tied",
            "fearin' you'll leave my side", 
            "and then I see the look in your eyes",
            "feeling I never really tried",
            ],
    },
    {
        numb: "I Will Survive, Gloria Gaynor",
        question: "I just walked in to find you here with __________, I should have changed that stupid lock",
        answer: "that sad look upon your face",
            options: [
            "that smug smirk in your lips",
            "that sad look upon your face", 
            "those warm eyes and cold words",
            "somebody else",
            ],
    },
    {
        numb: "Devuélveme a Mi Chica, Hombres G",
        question: "Ella se fue con un niño pijo tiene _________ y un jersey amarillo",
        answer: "un Ford fiesta blanco",
            options: [
            "un Ford fiesta blanco",
            "un Rolex dorado", 
            "ojos claros",
            "zapatos caros",
            ],
    },
    {
        numb: "Like a Virgin, Madonna",
        question: "Like a virgin with your ____ next to mine",
        answer: "heartbeat",
            options: [
            "body",
            "soul", 
            "heartbeat",
            "breathing",
            ],
    },
    {
        numb: "Girls Just Want to Have Fun, Cyndi Lauper",
        question: "My father yells: '_________' Oh daddy dear, you know you're still number one",
        answer: "what you gonna do with your life?",
            options: [
            "don't you dare to bring anyone home!",
            "you should focus on your studies!", 
            "who's that boy on the phone?",
            "what you gonna do with your life?",
            ],
    },
    
    {
        numb: "Veneno en la Piel, Radio Futura",
        question: "Y si esta noche quieres ir a bailar vete poniendo _______ pero tendrás que estar lista en media hora",
        answer: "el disfraz de pecadora",
            options: [
            "los tacones y tu corona",
            "el disfraz de pecadora", 
            "la ropa de ladrona",
            "tus ropas seductoras",
            ],
    },
    {
        numb: "It's Raining Men, The Weather Girls",
        question: "'Cause tonight for the first time _________ for the first time in history, it's gonna start saining men",
        answer: "just about half-past ten",
            options: [
            "as the thunders blare",
            "just about half-past ten", 
            "just before the night ends",
            "before the sun rises again",
            ],
    },
    {
        numb: "Y.M.C.A, Village People",
        question: "No man does it all by himself I said, young man, _______",
        answer: "put your pride on the shelf",
            options: [
            "no need to pride yourself",
            "put your pride on the shelf", 
            "you shall lower yourself",
            "forget your ego, don't pride yourself",
            ],
    },
    {
        numb: "Carolina, M-Clan",
        question: "La reina de las medicinas ______ vinagre para las heridas, dulce azúcal al final",
        answer: "que no se venden en farmacia legal",
            options: [
            "que no se venden en farmacia legal",
            "ella tiene una cura mortal", 
            "tan pequinosa como angelical",
            "soy su sujeto experimental",
            ],
    },
    {
        numb: "Tainted Love, Soft Cell",
        question: "And you think love is to pray but, I'm sorry, _______",
        answer: "I don't pray at all",
            options: [
            "I'm an atheist",
            "I don't believe in God", 
            "I don't pray at all",
            "My prayers belong to somebody else",
            ],
    },
    {
        numb: "Viva La Vida, Cold Play",
        question: "I used to __________ feel the fear in my enemy's eyes",
        answer: "roll the dice",
            options: [
            "be as cool as ice",
            "not ask but decide", 
            "roll the dice",
            "overflow with pride",
            ],
    },
    {
        numb: "Rosas, La Oreja de Van Gogh",
        question: "Allí me quedé, una mano en el corazón y en la otra ________",
        answer: "excusas que ni tú entendías",
            options: [
            "excusas que ni tú entendías",
            "ahogadas despedidas", 
            "rosas tornadas espigas",
            "caricias que ya no querías",
            ],
    },
    {
        numb: "La Taberna del Buda, Café Quijano",
        question: "Hay tres banqueros, van con corbata ______",
        answer: "están casados los anillos bien guardados",
            options: [
            "buscan aventuras de una noche",
            "queman en copas dinero sucio", 
            "están casados los anillos bien guardados",
            "en sus labios la marca carmín de la infidelidad",
            ],
    },
    {
        numb: "Eye of the Tiger, Survivor",
        question: "And the last know survivor ______ and he's watching us all with the eye of the tiger",
        answer: "stalks his prey in the night",
            options: [
            "stalks his prey in the night",
            "has the guts and the glory", 
            "is back on the street",
            "staks the oods",
            ],
    },
    {
        numb: "Bring Me To Life, Evanescence",
        question: "Wake me up inside, _________ and save me from the dark",
        answer: "call my name",
            options: [
            "reach out",
            "hold my hand", 
            "dry my tears",
            "call my name",
            ],
    },
    {
        numb: "Caperucita Feroz - Orquesta Mondragón",
        question: "Hola mi amor, yo soy tu lobo, te he coprado ________",
        answer: "un anillo, un pastel y un yoyó",
            options: [
            "rosas y una caperuza roja",
            "zapatos, pintalabios y un vestido", 
            "un perfume, un collar y un bombóm",
            "un anillo, un pastel y un yoyó",
            ],
    },

    {
        numb: "Thriller - Michael Jackson",
        question: "You feel the cold hand and ______, you close your eyes and hope that this is just imagination",
        answer: "wonder if you'll ever see the sun",
            options: [
            "and pray in sience for your life",
            "wonder if you'll ever see the sun", 
            "as horror looks you right between the eyes",
            "your body starts to shiver",
            ],
    },
    {
        numb: "Teenage Dirtbag, Wheatus",
        question: "Oh, how she rocks ________ but the doesn't know who I am",
        answer: "in Keds and tube socks",
            options: [
            "blue hair and pink top",
            "with hoses and lip-gloss", 
            "in joggers and bleached locks",
            "in Keds and tube socks",
            ],
    },
    // {
    //     numb: "Olvídame y Pega La Vuelta, Pimpinela",
    //     question: "Por eso vete, _________ y pega la vuelta",
    //     answer: "olvida mi nombre, mi cara, mi casa",
    //         options: [
    //         "olvida mi perfume, que me conociste",
    //         "olvídate de nosotros, de ti, de mí", 
    //         "olvida mi cara, mi voz, mis besos",
    //         "olvida mi nombre, mi cara, mi casa",
    //         ],
    // },
    {
        numb: "19 Días y 500 Noches",
        question: "Y regresé a la maldición __________ a la perdición de los bares de copas",
        answer: "del cajón sin su ropa",
            options: [
            "de noches lacrimosas",
            "de morenas, rubias y pelirrojas", 
            "del cajón sin su ropa",
            "de sábanas sin su aroma",
            ],
    },

]